guerrilla-games.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Guerrilla

Guerrilla-Games.com (the "Website") is operated by Guerrilla of Herengracht 601, 1017 CE Amsterdam, The Netherlands ("Guerrilla"). The information collected via this website is controlled by Guerrilla’s parent company, Sony Computer Entertainment Europe Limited of 10 Great Marlborough Street, London W1F 7LP (“SCEE”).  

### What kind of information do we collect?

We collect information submitted via the "Join" section of the Website, or e-mailed to us as part of a job application or job search process ("Application Information"). This information may include the applicant’s name, address, telephone number and email address, as well as resume or CV, cover letter, portfolio, and any other information relevant to the job application or job search process.

We also collect information submitted via the “Contact” section of the Website, including name, contact details and your message (“Contact Information”).  

In addition, we register visitor activity on the Website through the use of Google Analytics Cookies (see "What are cookies and how do we use them?", below).

### What do we do with the information we collect?

The Application Information we collect is used in a number of ways: 

  * To assess your skills, qualifications and interests against our career opportunities;
  * To verify your information and conduct reference checks;
  * To communicate with you and inform you of career opportunities;
  * To create and submit reports as required by law or regulation; and
  * To improve our recruitment process.

The Application Information is retained in accordance with local law. We may also retain Application Information to consider you for other jobs for which you may be qualified. If you accept employment with Guerrilla, the information collected will become part of your employment record and will be used for employment purposes.

We use Contact Information submitted via the “Contact” to respond to your message.

### Who else has access to your information?

Guerrilla employees, affiliated companies or entities acting on behalf of Guerrilla may have access to your Application Information for the purposes listed above. We take appropriate technical, organizational, and legal steps to protect your Application Information. Affiliate companies or entities acting on behalf of Guerrilla with whom we share your Application Information will be bound by terms of confidentiality and this Policy.

In exceptional circumstances, we may disclose your personal information if required by law or to protect or defend ourselves or others against illegal or harmful activities. If our business is sold or restructured, your details may be transferred as part of the business.

### What are cookies and how do we use them?

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Due to their core role of enhancing usability or site processes, disabling Cookies may prevent you from using certain websites. If you wish to learn how to enable, disable or delete Cookies, please consult the instructions or help functionality of your web browser.

This Website uses Cookies by Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). The information generated by the Cookies about your use of the Website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. We engage Google to do this in order to evaluate your use of the Website and compile reports on Website activity for us. We use this information to improve this and other websites.

For more information on the Cookies set by Google Analytics, including information on how to opt out, please visit <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html>. For more information on Cookies in general, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

### How can you contact us?

European data protection law provides individuals with certain rights to know what personal information an organisation holds about them and how that information is processed, as well as allowing them to seek amendment, blocking and erasure of such information, subject to some exceptions and conditions. If you would like to exercise any rights you may have, please contact us at [dpo@scee.net](mailto:dpo@scee.net) or write to SCEE at the address above.

### Changes to this policy

We may change this Policy from time to time. We will list any changes to the Policy at the bottom of this page.

### Changelog

  * _July 2, 2012:_  Initial version of the Privacy Policy document.
  *  _April 12, 2016:_ Updates to document structure and section headings to match new website.
  *  _May 26, 2016:_  Clarification that information collected via this Website is controlled by SCEE, Guerrilla’s parent company and also to remove and update provisions inconsistent with practice. No significant change to how your personal information is processed.
